freechildrenstories.com 2016-12-12

# Privacy Policy — FreeChildrenStories.com

## **Freechildrenstories.com  
Privacy Policy**

 _Last revised December 29, 2014_

 **1.   Background**

This privacy policy (our “ **Privacy Policy** ”) for Freechildrenstories.com (our “ **Website** ”) explains how we collect, use, and protect your information. Our User Agreement found at http://www.freechildrenstories.com/terms-of-use/ describes the legal obligations and restrictions you agree to in exchange for being allowed to access and use our Website. Our User Agreement and Privacy Policy are both equally important parts of the same agreement and form a legally binding contract between you and us and governs your use of the Website. Our User Agreement in particular includes many complicated legal promises and rules.

 **2.   Parental Consent—Children Under 18 Years Old**

 ** _If you are under 18 years old, do not use our Website until you have shared our User Agreement and our Privacy Policy with your parent or guardian._**

 **3.   Parental Consent—Children Under 13 Years Old**

If you are under 13 years of age you must get your parent’s permission before you use our Website or provide any information to us.

Children under age are not permitted to create an account on our Website or to comment on the stories on our Website.

 **NOTE TO PARENTS AND LEGAL GUARDIANS**. We are fully committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“ **COPPA** ”). Our Privacy Policy and User Agreement use “you” and “your” to identify you—the parent or legal guardian—and your child, on whose behalf you agree to our Privacy Policy and our User Agreement. Anywhere that we say “you” or “your” in our Privacy Policy and User Agreement, the word “you” means: (a) your child (b) you, as the parent expressly agreeing to be fully responsible for your child. Remember, the safety and protection of your children while online begins with your involvement and guidance. In addition the word “parent” means both parent and legal guardian. We do not disclose Personal Information regarding children under 13 years old to any third-parties. If you discover that your child has provided any Personal Information to us without your consent or if you simply wish to review or remove your child’s Personal Information from our lists, simply contact us at:

 **E-mail** : info@pajamapublishing.com

 **4.   Your Acceptance**

By accessing our Web site, meaning all content and functionality available through the freechildrenstories.com domain name, you agree to be legally bound by (a) our Privacy Policy and (b) our User Agreement found at http://www.freechildrenstories.com/useragreement and incorporated here by reference. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy or to our User Agreement, do not access our Website or provide us with any of your information.

 **5.   Personal Information**

Generally, we will try to limit the information we request from you. Depending on the circumstances, we might ask for some limited personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** ”) such as your first name and email address and the name and email address of your parent. We will only ever ask you information necessary for the specific activity that you request, and we do not condition your participation in any activity on you disclosing more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that specific activity.

We use your Personal Information only to allow you to access portions of our Website that you ask to access and to send communications and products that you specifically request.

We do not sell, transfer or share Personal Information with anyone other than people and companies we engage to prepare or deliver the communications or products you request or to perform related technical and processing functions. We require that any third party who receives access to your Personal Information agrees to maintain your confidentiality. And we never disclose Personal Information regarding children under age 13 to any third-parties.

Your parent may at any time review, change, or delete any Personal Information that we have collected about you by contacting us at:

 **E-mail** : info@pajamapublishing.com

 **6.   Usage Information**

We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your Web browser, including your Internet Protocol (“ **IP address** ”), the page you request, and how long and how often you visit any page on our Website. When you use our Website, our servers log certain information that your Web browser sends when you visit any Web site. Our server logs may include information such as your Web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

We allow third-party advertisers to serve advertisements on our Website. These third-party advertisers use technology that sends advertisements and links directly to your browser, and they automatically receive your IP address when this happens. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party advertisers without your consent, except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. If you respond to an advertisement, the advertiser may conclude that you fit the description of the audience the advertiser is trying to reach. The advertiser may also use non-personally identifiable information regarding your use of our Website, such as the number of times you viewed an ad, to determine which ads to deliver to you.

We use cookies on our Website. Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a Web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for Web sites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your Web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information from scratch upon each visit to a given Web site. We serve a cookie from our Web site when members log in to member-only pages, so that they can navigate those pages on the site. A randomly-generated anonymous identifier is assigned to that cookie to enable this process. We also serve a cookie to note the anonymous web traffic described in this section of this Privacy Policy.

We participate in the Google Adsense network, which serves the DoubleClick DART cookie. You may opt out of use of the DART cookie and participation in many other third-party advertising networks by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, available at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

 **7.   How We Use Information We Collect**

If you are over 13 years old, we may use your Personal Information to contact you, respond to your inquiries, and send you other information we think may be of interest to you, such as special offers or to notify you of important new changes to our Website. If you are under 13 years of age, we will only use your Personal Information to provide you with services and information that you have specifically requested and that we have your parents’ permission to provide.

 **8.   Warning Regarding Posting Your Personal Information**

Any Personal Information (for example, your name, e-mail address, or personal photographs) that you voluntarily disclose in comments or on any bulletin board, message board, or other community forum on our website may be collected and used by parties other than us and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.

If you post personal information on any publicly accessible part of our Website, such as in the comments or on a message board, we have no control over how others use your personal information. We are not responsible for what happens to personal information that you post on any publicly accessible part of our Website.

 **9.   Restriction on Posting Personal Information—Children Under 13 Years Old**

If you are under 13 years old, you are not permitted to post any personal information to a publicly accessible part of our Website, including in the comments and on any message board.

If you believe that any child under age 13 has posted personal information anywhere on our Website, please contact us immediately at info@pajamapublishing.com and provide as much information as you can to help us locate and delete the personal information.

If you are under 13 years old and you post any personal information to a publicly accessible part of our Website, we may, but are not required, to: (a) delete the personal information; (b) immediately terminate your account; and (c) contact your parents regarding the posting.

 **10.   Disclosure Of Your Information**

We may disclose your Personal Information in any of these circumstances:

·  when we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who might be infringing our rights or property, or the rights and property of any one else.

·  to enforce our User Agreement, take precautions against liability, investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, or protect the security or integrity of our Website.

·  in response to judicial process.

·  in cooperation with law enforcement agency investigations of matters related to public safety

·  if we have a good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary to comply with state and federal laws.

·  to identify and develop products and services that may be of interest to you or to share this information with certain third parties for direct marketing purposes, except we will never disclose Personal Information related to children under age 13.

·  if we have your consent and you are age 13 or older.

 **11.   Transfer**

We may sell or buy other businesses or entities. If we do, we may transfer or assign the information we have collected, including your Personal Information, as part of the purchase or sale. Also, in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used and your Personal Information may be included in the transferred assets. We do not sell Personal Information, to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future. Under the laws of some jurisdictions, you may be entitled to request disclosure regarding how we share non-personally identifiable information about you with third parties for direct marketing purposes (“ **Information-Sharing Disclosure** ”). To the extent required by law, we will provide the Information-Sharing Disclosure to you upon request made to:

 **Email:** info@pajamapublishing.com

 **12.   Opting-Out**

You may opt-out of receiving any communications for which you have signed up at any time by clicking on a link provided at the bottom of the email communication or by contacting info@pajamapublishing.com. If you are a California resident, you have the right to decline to have your personal information shared with third-parties. If you wish to exercise this right, contact us at info@pajamapublishing.com ; please include the following in your e-mail: (a) a statement that you decline to have your personal information shared with third parties; (b) your name; (c) your e-mail address; and (d) your mailing address. Remember, if you are under age 13, we will never disclose your personal information to third parties.

 **13.   Linked Sites**

Our Website may include links to other Web sites. Each linked Web site will have its own policies concerning how it collects, uses, and discloses your personal information.  **These Web sites are not part of our Website.**

You should carefully review all policies and agreements you visit any Web site. We are not responsible for and we do not have any control over other Web sites.

We do not endorse, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any product or service advertised or offered by a third party through our Website or any Website linked or featured in any advertising featured on our Web site.

 **14.   Security Procedures**

We take reasonable precautions and have implemented reasonable technical measures intended to protect against the risks of unauthorized access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of Personal Information submitted using our Website. But your e-mail transmissions and other communications containing Personal Information might be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and the Website might be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative errors.

 **We cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the Internet**.

When we receive your Personal Information, we take steps that we believe are reasonable to limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees and service providers whom we determine need access to the Personal Information to provide the products, services, offers, or opportunities that you have requested. But even after we receive your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of our reasonable efforts or as a result of any event beyond our reasonable control. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee that your Personal Information is completely secure and safe from such risks.

 **15.   Disclaimer of Warranties**

We disclaim any express or implied warranty regarding the security of any information we collect about you.

 **16.   Changes and Updates to Our Privacy Policy**

We may revise our Privacy Policy and User Agreement at any time. To help you stay current with any changes, we note the date the Privacy Policy or User Agreement was last updated. Using our Website after we amend our Privacy Policy or User Agreement signifies that you accept the revised terms, so we strongly recommend that you periodically check our User Agreement and Privacy Policy.
